<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="empty"></string>
    <string name="app_name">O Tannenbaum</string>
    <string name="not_available">N/A</string>
    <string name="lot_phone">phone:</string>
    <string name="lot_hours">hours:</string>
    <string name="tab_otannenbaum">#otannenbaum</string>
    <string name="tab_types">types</string>
    <string name="tab_care">care</string>
    <string name="option_lots">Lots</string>
    <string name="option_dropsites">Dropsites</string>
    <string name="lot_verified">V E R I F I E D</string>

    <string name="add_lot_business">Business Name</string>
    <string name="add_lot_cross">Cross Streets</string>
    <string name="add_lot_landmark">Nearest Landmark</string>
    <string name="add_lot_phone">Phone</string>
    <string name="add_lot_hours">Hours</string>


    <string name="add_lot_amex">American Express</string>
    <string name="add_lot_visa">Visa</string>
    <string name="add_lot_mastercard">Mastercard</string>
    <string name="add_lot_discover">Discover</string>

    <string name="types_content_douglar_fir_title">Douglas Fir</string>
    <string name="types_content_douglas_fir">Long soft blue-green needles and a sweet fragrance with flexible, medium
        weight branches. Branches can be difficult to safely hang ornaments on depending on shearing technique.
    </string>
    <string name="types_content_balsam_fir_title">Balsam Fir</string>
    <string name="types_content_balsam_fir">Medium length very soft needles with a slightly tapered shape, the tree is
        full and has strong branches and excellent needle retention. Very fragrant tree that exudes the scent of
        Christmas.
    </string>
    <string name="types_content_fraser_fir_title">Fraser Fir</string>
    <string name="types_content_fraser_fir">Short, soft and rounded at the tip needles with a deep green on the topside
        of the needle and a silver tint underside. Standard fir fragrance with an extremely lengthy life after being
        cut, able to be put up throughout the entire season.
    </string>
    <string name="types_content_white_pine_title">White Pine</string>
    <string name="types_content_white_pine">Soft and flexible with bluish-green to silver green needles ranging from 2.5
        to 5" in length. Needles have excellent retention however the trees fragrance is mild. Struggles with heavier
        ornaments due to the branch size.
    </string>
    <string name="types_content_grand_fir_title">Grand Fir</string>
    <string name="types_content_grand_fir">Dark green and shiny needles with a silvery underside which are 1 - 1.5" in
        length. Needle retention is good. Exudes a citrus like aroma that makes this one of the strongest and most
        appealing trees for those craving scent.
    </string>
    <string name="types_content_noble_fir_title">Noble Fir</string>
    <string name="types_content_noble_fir">Bluish green needles that evoke a silvery appearance. It has shorter, stiff
        branches which work well for heavier ornaments. Needle retention is excellent and wreaths are commonly made from
        this type.
    </string>

    <string name="care_content">
        "Displaying trees in water in a traditional reservoir type stand is the most effective way of maintaining their
        freshness and minimizing needle loss problems.

        Make a fresh cut to remove about a 1/2-inch thick disk of wood from the base of the trunk before putting the
        tree in the stand. Make the cut perpendicular to the stem axis. Don't cut the trunk at an angle, or into a
        v-shape, which makes it far more difficult to hold the tree in the stand and also reduces the amount of water
        available to the tree.

        Once home, place the tree in water as soon as possible. Most species can go 6 to 8 hours after cutting the trunk
        and still take up water. Don't bruise the cut surface or get it dirty.

        If needed, trees can be temporarily stored for several days in a cool location. Place the freshly cut trunk in a
        bucket that is kept full of water.

        To display the trees indoors, use a stand with an adequate water holding capacity for the tree. As a general
        rule, stands should provide 1 quart of water per inch of stem diameter. Devices are available that help maintain
        a constant water level in the stand.

        Use a stand that fits your tree. Avoid whittling the sides of the trunk down to fit a stand. The outer layers of
        wood are the most efficient in taking up water and should not be removed.

        Keep trees away form major sources of heat (fireplaces, heaters, heat vents, direct sunlight).

        Lowering the room temperature will slow the drying process, resulting in less water consumption each day.

        The temperature of the water used to fill the stand is not important and does not affect water uptake.

        Check the stand daily to make sure that the level of water does not go below the base of the tree. With many
        stands, there can still be water in the stand even though the base of the tree is no longer submerged in water.

        Drilling a hole in the base of the trunk does NOT improve water uptake.

        Use of lights that produce low heat, such as miniature lights, will reduce drying of the tree."
    </string>
</resources>
